What's wrong with these eggs?
A Stand…
Pale Snake is no longer my Stand ability.
Something else is inside me… but what?
I feel terrible…
Something is running loose inside me.
This power, it's beyond my control.
But this power carries hope.
I can at least feel
hope within this power.
Dio's memo inside Jotaro's memory…
It seems this power needs
the things in that memory.
Time and place.
North latitude, 28 degrees 24 minutes.
West longitude, 80 degrees 36 minutes.
That's where heaven will be.
This location is Cape Canaveral.
Kennedy Space Center.
In the beginning of all matter,
there was gravity.
Even for this earth,
gravity was its beginning.
What's going on?
At this rate, we're going to fall!
We aren't falling down, but sideways!
Is this the priest's ability?
Jolyne! Don't let go of Emporio!
Diver Drive!
Ermes!
Gravity keeps the planets revolving.
Where shall I head on this earth now?
What is going to transpire?
This is the power my father sealed
in Egypt 20 years ago.
This is what the priest called "heaven"!
To my body and mind…
and to the end of all things?
That's the entrance to the Visitor Center…
Jolyne, the priest is still here, right?
Yes, he's close. He's almost within reach.
It's as if he was just here.
The priest's Stand evolved!
My right hand!
EPISODE 34: SEE MOON (1)
I came to finish you off now,
if you can't wait two days.
Jolyne Cujoh!
My arm is turning inside out!
- Jolyne!
So you are the one who's been
helping Jolyne this whole time.
Emporio, get behind Anastasia!
Stone Ocean!
Jolyne, behind you!
I'll get rid of Jolyne Cujoh first.
Anastasia, get over here. Hurry!
What is this Stand?
Your strands turned inside out!
It turned my spike inside out too!
That's where his fist touched,
but it was merely a scratch!
We have to stay away from his attacks!
It must be gravity.
Think of the events leading up to now!
The stand ability must be
related to gravity!
All matters including the Earth and apples
are affected by gravity.
Gravity attracts matter
towards the center of mass!
That's the cosmic law!
This Stand ability alters gravity
and changes its direction!
Anything that touches its fist
turns inside out.
I don't know its range,
but it makes everything fall sideways!
So that's how the weak gravity
at Cape Canaveral
affected and evolved the priest's Stand!
Its powers are completely different
from Pale Snake's memory manipulation,
nor is it The Green Baby's power
of infinite division.
Jolyne, it's coming to strike again!
Go to Anastasia, Emporio!
It took a hit!
Impossible!
My leg is inverting!
Jolyne!
This can't be!
Don't panic, Emporio.
You can relax.
If everything it touches turns inside out,
then I'll let it hit me again
to revert my body back right side out.
Turn my body inside out…
and outwards again!
Jolyne!
Good grief.
Of course,
I have to stitch the wounds.
One thing is for certain now.
Every strike I deal leaves damage!
If I have to strike it down
here and now, then…
We have no time to waste.
Climb, Emporio.
Get to the guardrails.
I'm here as Jolyne's backup,
not your babysitter!
I'm going!
Jolyne!
I already turned
this ticketing box office inside out!
The way it moves…
Judging by the powers,
I thought it was an auto-tracking Stand,
but the attacks are too accurate!
As if it knows that it's useless,
so it's no longer targeting
my arms and legs.
It's now aiming for my vitals
like my head and chest,
the only places that would be fatal!
It dodged my kicks
with machine-like precision!
This Stand is a remote control type!
The priest's eyes are watching.
This Stand's attacks are precise
because the priest can see the fight!
Its attacks only seem destructive
because its power
is amplified by gravity.
Where is he?
I assumed he was hiding, but he's close!
He is close enough from here
to see us clearly!
Diver Drive!
Stay down.
Anastasia!
I said, I'll get rid of Jolyne first.
Anastasia, Jolyne!
Stone Ocean!
Jolyne!
What did you do, Jolyne?
Anastasia!
You might be able to help yourself.
It's easy for you to jump on the pavement,
but for now, don't let go of my rope.
Your weight is choking our foe.
The Stand is powerless!
Not only that, it doesn't have
the strength to break free!
Unbelievable!
It's trying to grab Jolyne's string
before it suffocates!
If it grabs Jolyne's rope with its hands…
The thread will turn inside out
and disintegrate!
Jolyne, let go of its neck.
I did this to free you from its grasp!
No, Anastasia. I have to face it now.
Our chance is now,
with the rope around its neck!
I'm not trying to strangle it.
I'll close in and finish it off!
What are you saying, Jolyne?
If it grabs a hold of this rope,
it will invert your thread.
Then your arm will get inverted as well!
Damn you!
I'll reach you in no time, just you wait!
No matter what I say, Jolyne won't listen.
We're in a horrible situation.
Fuck it!
If you're finishing it off, then be quick!
Hurry up and break free!
Ah, he grabbed her rope!
No, I still have time.
My thread
will stay intact just a moment longer!
STAND NAME: SEE MOON
STAND MASTER: FATHER PUCCHI
This is Sigma Team.
It's no good, we can't go any further.
The tank flipped over!
Get any closer to the Visitor Center,
and the tank flips upside down!
What do you mean, "the tank flips?"
Report!
It's just as I said.
The tank flips over!
Some force is flipping the tank over.
We can't figure it out.
Please send scientists or experts
to investigate.
Don't try to figure it out.
Our mission is to rescue the victims!
Still, we really have no idea
what's going on.
We don't know if there are survivors,
or how big the affected area is.
The entire place is a mess.
What is going on?
It's as if a hammer fell from the sky
and pounded onto the ground,
and turned the area into a scrapyard!
This is J-Hawk 9.
I have vision on the center.
It's three kilometers away.
Attempting to locate the survivors.
What the hell?
Which way is up?
Mayday!
J-Hawk 9?
J-Hawk 9!
What happened? Do you copy?
J-Hawk 6, do you copy?
This is our opportunity
to defeat the priest's Stand!
But this is too risky!
Jolyne's arm is getting shredded!
Don't waste your time!
Hurry up and finish it off!
Stone Ocean!
It's inverting the steel plating
to stand itself up!
Hurry! Hurry up and finish it!
This is hopeless,
it's almost all the way up!
It ripped more tiles off!
It grabbed her string!
Jolyne, let go of it!
You have to run!
Your arm will get shredded!
Diver Drive!
I submerged Diver Drive into the rope.
And now, instead of Jolyne's rope,
my body will turn inside out!
Anastasia.
Get it, Jolyne. As long as your string
is wrapped around its neck,
I won't let it get up!
- Anastasia!
- Now go! End this fight, Jolyne!
After all, it was in my best interest
to get rid of you when I had the chance.
When you were in prison,
at the very beginning.
Jesus bore the fate of being crucified.
Mary, Mother of Jesus,
was fated to lose her son.
To achieve happiness,
humans must bear a curse,
and overcome fate.
The trial Dio and I had to overcome
was Joestar's bloodline.
This can't be…
The priest is here!
I have come to save my Stand,
which is still undergoing evolution.
What?
My body is rising towards the sky!
I am the center of gravity.
Gravity is reversed wherever I stand.
The closer you come to me,
the stronger the gravity gets.
The last step is to bide my time
until my ability fully evolves.
It will harness even greater power,
not the little strength it has now.
Anastasia, pull on her rope!
I'm trying already!
Listen closely, my Stand.
I'll say this again. Invert her only once.
Do not strike more than once.
The attack to a vital area
is more devastating
than one to the arms or body.
Remember, a single punch will do.
Splendid.
We shall return to the Visitor Center.
What?
The fight is over.
Jolyne can no longer feel pain
or even think.
Her heart was turned inside out,
reversing the blood flow to her brain.
Anastasia, pull her close!
Hurry, draw her in!
Jolyne's strings…
No…
This can't be happening!
Jolyne!
This ability,
I shall name it See Moon.
Invincibility.
Did I gain invincibility
before the new moon?
However, my ultimate goal
does not lie in simply achieving strength.
I shall remind myself that my pursuit
is the happiness of all human beings.
Jolyne Cujoh is no more than a casualty,
just like Weather and the prisoners
whose lives were sacrificed.
To successfully achieve a goal,
trial and sacrifice is inevitable.
I don't believe this.
What should I do, Jolyne?
What happened just now…
No, this can't be happening!
What's that?
Where is that sound coming from?
It's the phone!
It didn't have a signal a moment ago.
I got a new message.
Who is it from?
My calls aren't going through.
The gravitational anomaly seems to
have sent a satellite out of orbit.
Are you Emporio?
I don't know exactly what's going on,
but I can sense that my daughter
and the priest have met.
Could this be…
Is this him?
Is this message from…
Jolyne is alive.
But she's not safe.
Protect Jolyne.
Just until I arrive… that's all I ask.
She must have discovered how to
counter his gravity.
That's the only way
she could have survived.
She's alive, but just barely.
Jotaro Kujo.
It's Mr. Jotaro!
He's nearby!
I don't believe this.
Jolyne is alive!
That means…
No, this can't be!
Anastasia, find Jolyne!
Jolyne isn't dead!
What?
But the priest knows too,
because he must've sensed
that she's alive!
What did you do, Jolyne Cujoh?
Your heart was turned inside out!
Gravity imploded your heart!
How could she still be alive?
How did she manage to survive?
We must settle the score.
The Joestar bloodline must be overcome!
Diver Drive!
Where are you going?
Isn't it obvious?
The best way to protect Jolyne
is to kill that priest!
MARCH 21ST, 2012 11:44 AM
36 HOURS AND 16 MINUTES UNTIL THE NEW MOON
Subtitle translation by: Megumi Hunter